at midnight the wildly popular Emmy
winning late night panel show hosted by
J crew Aaron Paul is about
to throw up in away message and
disappear from television oh that's us
oh
guys yeah well you know you should you
should have watched the show more I
don't that's on you you know what
you how about
thatly what are they going to do cancel
us again
uh people ask why we're leaving and the
answer is it it is just it just felt
like the right time you know we did the
show for four years and we started it
was very Innovative and I think we've
given out as many points as possible Ron
funes has them all uh how many more
hashtags can we do you know like
honestly I I we thought we were going to
run out of hashtags in season one uh and
we didn't we stretched it to four
somehow uh and in a way this is great
news for people who don't want to see
their Twitter feeds overrun four nights
a week with our like # soup politics or
whatever ad goat ruin a Broadway show or
whatever it is uh on second that those
are great uh write those down guys billy
goat Elliott kid on a hot ttin roof
Chicago and we're canceled again all
right anyway all of us at the show are
incredibly grateful to the network we
incredibly grateful to you we are
incredibly grateful to the fans this has
been a dream job for me it is an amazing
staff and crew I've had an amazing time
time doing this uh thanks for making
dick shows jokes with us for the past
four years and you know all I can say is
this is very celebratory it's very rare
that you get to do your dream job and we
got to do it for four years 600 times
almost by the time it's done 600 one two
emys and um and I just want to say
thanks it's been an absolute pleasure
to I always CH creeping into your houses
at
night so comedians since that midnight
is going away what should our Lash # war
Travis hash anyone need a writing
staff yes points oh my God we just no I
want them to get work yeah actually I'm
helping Justin Tony 2017 let's yes all
right Griffin Chris I'm more worried
about the hashtag waron Christmas all
right
yeah